Hello, we are the Morisaka Morisaka generation!
Yes, we just came back from a successful coming-of-age ceremony!
Thank you very much!
I'd like to start off by introducing some of the points of that cute furisodes of ours.
AVBA Furumizusaka-kun
Se-no!
Wow!
Do you have any points?
What is the point?
My favorite light blue color.
Also, the sparkles here
is so cute and
and it has a very luxurious feel.
And I used my favorite color, green.
Oh, that's nice.
I'm going to take you for a spin.
Wow, and the hair.
And your hair.
What's going on?
It's a lot of twirling.
Oh, it's beautiful.
It was like this.
Wow.
What's the point?
I started talking to him.
Yes, you did.
This slightly darker color
The bright orange in this darker color.
There's a pattern of the king of kings here.
This is a Japanese flower called rikka.
It has a very old-fashioned or Japanese feel to it.
I'm glad I was able to wear it for my coming-of-age ceremony.
Let's go around the circle.
Yes!
So cute!
Ta-da!
It's bright red... but I chose red... because I wanted it to be more mature... and I wanted the red to have a little more depth than normal red.
I wanted a more mature look, so I added a little black and white to the red.
The obi's cool, too.
Hair ornament is stylish, too.
Come out, come out!
What do you think?
I went with pure white for the hair ornament.
I borrowed it from my sister.
The obi is amazing. I'm wearing a tulip pattern.
I've never seen anything like it.
It's sweet, but the background music is really cool.
Like this. Thank you very much.
It's so cute!
The main point is that I think of 20 years old as a big stairway to adulthood, so I wanted to make it look a little more mature.
I decided to use black and other cool colors to make it look a little more mature.
Please hold the stone.
It's so cute! The watermark is so cute!
It's a straight polly. It's beautiful.
It's a straight polly. It's really nice. It's got a great style.
The mizuhiki is really nice.
It's so nice! Thank you so much!
Thank you very much.
What's your point?
I chose navy blue. I think this color makes my skin look the most beautiful.
I chose this color because I thought it would make my skin look the most beautiful.
It's also pretty on your hair.
It's true, it's true, it's true, it's true.
I was obsessive about it, and it took me about 20 days to find it.
It looks great on you. It's so cute.
It's cute. It's cute. It's sparkly.
I want you to come by the house.
It's a sparkly drink.
It's not just the pearls, it's the sparkles.
They were homegrown.
That's pretty. Thank you.
It's so pretty.
I wanted to add the siren's color, light blue, and a little purple, Nagasaka's purple.
But since I'm 20 years old, I wanted to use a more mature color, a little grayish.
I'm 20 years old, so I wanted a more mature color with a grayish tinge.
Miikun gray, which is very rare.
It has pearls and prills.
It's a little more modern and contemporary.
I chose this color with some green here and there.
It's so cute!
I've never seen Mii's knot before.
Is it cute?
I thought the prills were very Miikyun-like.
Her hair is cute too.
I put a lot of flowers. Thank you.
Here we go.
What's your point?
My name is Sakura, so I wanted to wear a cherry blossom colored dress.
So I decided on cherry blossom color.
It's so cute! It looks great on you.
You said you wanted me to wear a classic pattern.
So I took his advice and went with a classic pattern.
So cute! Your hair is amazing!
So much pink and pearls.
But it looks so short.
It's cute. There's pearls here, too.
A little bit more modern here.
Yeah, it's very modern.
Not too much.
It's very pretty.
Thank you very much.
I wrote one kanji character for this year's goal.
I'd like to introduce them one by one.
Let's start with you, Rei-chan.
I chose "myself.
I chose the character for "myself.
When I turned 20 years old, I had to make many choices,
I used to listen to the opinions of many people,
I used to listen to many people's opinions and worry a lot,
I used to listen to many people's opinions and worry a lot, but now I am responsible for what I want to do,
I wanted to take responsibility for what I wanted to do, what interested me, and what excited me,
Hmmm.
I want to be independent from now on,
Self-sufficiency,
I will do my best. I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I wrote the kanji character for happiness.
This is because I have received a lot of happiness since I joined Nogizaka and I became friends with many seniors last year.
I was able to get to know many of my seniors and even my classmates better. The bonds amongst our peers have also deepened.
I feel that this job gives me a lot of happiness on a daily basis, so I would like to convey happiness to them next.
I would like to convey happiness to others.
I wrote the kanji character for happiness because I want to be the one who distributes it to those around me.
Next year... not next year.
I beg you.
I wrote the character for "tadasu.
It has many meanings.
I think 20 is a very immortal age.
I think it's a year of immortality, so it also means to switch my mind and make things right.
And also because my rhythm of life is over.
But really, since the beginning of the year, I've been able to live a regular life.
I wrote the character for "correct" in order to maintain a regular rhythm in my life.
I will do my best.
Yes, I wrote the character for know.
Yes, I think that at the age of 20, I have become an adult,
I chose this kanji because I want to acquire intelligence in order to become a wonderful woman from now on.
I will do my best to become a mature woman.
Please help me.
I chose the Chinese character for "believe.
This year, I will try to believe in the things around me and in myself, and I will also try to be trusted by various people.
I also chose this character because I hope to become a person who can be trusted by various people.
I will do my best.
Let's see... I chose the character for "beautiful.
I chose the character for "beautiful.
I love all my names.
If I had to choose one character out of all of them
I chose this character because I love all my names and I think it's beauty.
Now that I am 20 years old and an adult
I would like to do my best to become a beautiful person like my seniors.
I beg you.
You are already beautiful.
Aishin
I chose a dragon. I drew an illustration of a dragon here.
I drew this illustration of a dragon here, and I want to do my best together as a generation of dragons.
I am sure that the bond between the eight of us is very strong, so I drew this illustration with the hope that we can do something together.
Thank you very much for your cooperation during the distribution.
I drew the character for "abundance.
I wrote it so that I can spend the year peacefully.
Also, my hometown is Toyohashi.
I also wrote the character for "abundance" to express my wish to spend the year in abundance.
Lastly, I would like to try my luck.
There are 8 cups, and yes, there are 8 cups.
Seven of them contain citric acid and are acidic.
Seven of them are sour, and only one of them can drink normal water.
How about that one lucky girl?
New Year's greetings. From me?
What? Really?
This is for you.
Careful!
It's too backwards, isn't it?
Yes, one is citric acid.
I'll just take it out.
I have no idea.
D1.
By the looks of it, it's probably Japanese.
I see, something, but I'm sure it's light... this is shiny.
It's glowing.
Higashiyama Catch Can
Scary.
So it's not enough?
It's not safe to put too much on the bottom.
Yes, I got it.
It's better not to put too much on the bottom.
Okay, I'll take it.
Cheers?
I'll drink to that.
Congratulations on your chicken.
Thank you very much.
Se-no.
Oh, don't knock it, ai.
This is great!
You guys look so cute
Oh, no!
I ate a little bit of it downstairs.
What?
Oh, my mouth hurts.
Oh, that hurts.
What does it taste like? Like lemon?
No, not really.
It's like 50 times more lemon.
Lemons are fruity.
It's not about taste.
It's just sourness.
Okay, so the lucky girl was Luna.
Yay!
Did you take the last picture?
I took the last one.
And the rest.
There is fortune in leftovers.
This year, I will take pictures of the leftovers.
Well, now that we have come of age, we will do our best to tell a new ghost story,
I will do my best to tell a new ghost story as a member of the adult community,
I would like to ask for everyone's cooperation.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you in the future.